[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 22]
Immortal,
I've heard about
what has happened from Master Shang.
But we can't break the rules in Immortal Palace.
If such an important criminal
wants to leave Litian Temple,
she must be punished by three thunderbolts.
You mean
whether Liu Shao is innocent or not,
she has to be punished with three thunderbolts if she wants to leave, right?
Senior,
I don't think she can stand one thunderbolt now,
let alone three thunderbolts,
Think about it.
If Liu Shao is wronged,
she's already miserable enough now.
Do we have to kill her?
Even if she is wronged,
it's Immortal's responsibility.
Isn't this punishment given to her
because Immortal agreed?
The rules in Immortal Palace cannot be abolished.
Her grievance
is indeed my fault.
I'll be punished
instead of her.
Master Zhuo,
I wonder what will happen
after these three thunderbolts.
Liu Shao will be at your disposal.
The three palaces won't doubt anything.
It is a deal.
♫The wind is getting slower, while the pear flowers are dropping♫
Please seal your spiritual power.
Then, the punishment of thunder can get close to your body.
♫The silver color is cold and sharp♫
Sure.
Within the three whips, there are no class differences.
Everyone in the three palaces can stop me.
♫On the top of Heaven and between reincarnation♫
After three whips when the punishment of thunder has passed,
I will not yield a step.
♫The moon is like snow♫
Whatever Liu Shao's crime is,
I am willing to be punished with her.
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
One.
♫The wind is getting slower, while the pear flowers are dropping♫
♫The silver color is cold and sharp♫
♫On the top of Heaven and between reincarnation♫
♫The moon is like snow♫
Two.
Senior.
♫I carve our appointment in three days between my eyebrows♫
♫I walk through time with you♫
♫On the day when seas sink♫
♫When the moon never rests, the mortal world♫
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
Three.
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
I'll take you back now.
♫You left my heart. You are my fate♫
♫You are like dreams as if you disappear♫
♫Two sides are round. You are like the moon at 11 pm♫
♫You are my fate♫
♫Look at the three realms. Look at the wilderness♫
♫Our old fate has become a cocoon♫
I will find out the truth
♫The rest of life is no match for a second♫
about Immortal Master Wanwu being assassinated
and explain to you.
♫I look back to realize the dream of my next life♫
♫Half of my heart is yours. Half of me is missing you♫
♫I pay my life to fulfill my dream♫
♫You nag about days and nights beside my ear, but I can't hear you♫
♫The night carves the heart into poems♫
I will not leave.
Luo Ge,
Don't think too much.
Have a good rest.
Don't go.
Don't go...
Liu Shao,
the person you've been unwilling to lose is Lu Li.
And Lu Li is also me.
From now on,
Luo Ge is Lu Li.
I'll stand in front of you,
trust you,
and protect you.
No.
This must be a dream.
Luo Ge wouldn't say these to me.
Whether it's a dream or not,
I will never let you go again.
Cultivating for
thousands of years lonesomely
is not good at all.
But someone has to experience the loneliness of thousands of years
to protect peace in the Three Realms.
Liu Shao, Liu Shao.
Immortal, Immortal,
how's Liu Shao?
I heard that Liu Shao's energy pill was badly damaged.
Is she okay now?
She's fine now.
She hasn't woken up yet.
Don't disturb her.
Immortal,
I am King Herb aged 10 thousand years.
If a mortal smells me,
all diseases will be cured.
If I stay beside Liu Shao,
with the herbal fragrance accompanying her,
she can recover faster.
Go ahead now.
She has already gone down the mountain.
How could this happen?
I thought I could give you Weirui Grass, and
I could go to Liu Mansion
to see the pear tree at her home.
Wait.
I wonder if you have medicine
for internal injury.
The harp lacks a string.
Legend has it that
fairies' hair
can be strings.
Fu.
It doesn't work.
Fu,
I will save you.
Rong,
you also think that the measures I took are drastic.
Although there is a strong possibility that Liu Shao is framed,
I insisted on executing the punishment of thunder.
You think I am too cruel and inhumane,
right?
Actually, I understand.
Senior, as the master of Palace Wuxie,
you take charge of the penalty.
You only care about rules and regulations.
It is the same for yourself
and for others.
You were not targeting Luo Ge.
No, I was targeting Luo Ge.
I even targeted many people.
I understand.
After my father died,
Palace Chonghua became more and more powerful,
while Palace of Abyssal Mirrors is not as powerful as Palace Chonghua.
You
were entrusted by my father.
But I am not good enough, and I am laughed at by others,
so you're always against others.
You did it for me.
You know everything,
but you always pretend not to know.
Rong,
I've had enough
as your senior.
I want to be more than just your junior,
Senior.
Is it two hours?
I'll get you some water.
No need.
Move slowly.
It seems that
you are fine.
Bone-Corroding Harp is
really a healing halidom.
Rumors are true.
Could it be that
I am really...
Does the immortal energy in my body
really belong to
the Immortal Ze Shui who died in the demon clan?
No wonder...
no wonder my brother...
He is him.
You are you.
Fate never starts again.
I never believe in fate.
Don't believe it either.
Let me see the wound on your hand.
I don't know what's wrong with Bone-Corroding Harp.
It can't even cure my wound.
It is because
you only cared about me.
It's a little itchy.
Actually, I want to ask
what you are going to do
with Bone-Corroding Harp.
I'll put it back to Palace of Abyssal Mirrors
and pretend nothing has happened.
My brother doesn't want me to know it
because he wants to protect me.
I understand.
I'll protect him too,
secretly.
I understand.
It is just like how I want to protect my brother.
And
I want to protect you
and let you be a happy little fairy.
Fu, look,
the restriction is lifted.
Does this mean
my brother and Liu Shao are safe?
He really thinks that I am so old and stupid
that I can't recognize the murderer.
Immortal Luo Ge has sent a message.
He said that he would find out the truth.
What truth?
The truth is that he is bewitched by Liu Shao
and keeps protecting her.
I don't need his medicine.
Return it to him.
Immortal Master has such prejudice against Liu Shao.
Yes.
If I hadn't remembered the past,
I'd probably be the same.
This is...
spell.
Brother!
Brother, what's the matter?
I'm fine.
I have...
been busy lately.
I need to calm down.
I'm glad you're fine.
I've heard about
what happened in Litian Temple.
Although we haven't found the murderer,
fortunately, Immortal Master and Liu Shao are fine.
Brother, don't worry too much.
I'm not worried.
After these,
I will check your schoolwork.
Don't slack off.
Brother,
do you mean
those scriptures that you let me recite?
I've already memorized them.
You can check at any time.
Okay.
I won't disturb you.
I'll go back first.
Tomorrow,
I'll bring you
some fragrance to help you calm down,
OK?
Okay.
I'm leaving.
I'm devoted to cultivating.
I won't have Lu Li's feelings.
You have his feelings.
I heard that Lu Li was cursed by Soul-Devouring Spell.
He couldn't break it even when he died.
Look, do I have it?
It turns out that
I really have it.
It comes out from the heart
and arrives with love.
Luo Ge!
Liu Shao,
you're finally awake.
Try it and see what soup this is.
You haven't eaten food for a long time.
It is water shield soup.
There are some bamboo shoots
and saury.
In the mortal world,
these food are in season.
I thought you would like it,
so I let you try it.
It's been a while since
I left the mortal world.
The seasonal dishes at home
are made by my mother in person.
My father often said that
with my mother's cooking skills,
even if she broke his legs,
he wouldn't leave home.
I once thought of
bringing a person home and
trying my mother's cooking.
Do you still wish to do that?
Immortal
has a conscience.
He went to Litian Temple for you
and got you back.
Do you mean that
Luo Ge sent me back?
Yes.
He even accepted three thunderbolts for you.
Otherwise, Master Zhuo wouldn't let you go.
That silly man
is a bit dull,
but he's still on your side.
He thought he was smart.
But Master knew it right away that
he fed you Weirui Grass.
Master,
are you telling the truth?
Absolutely.
Except for Weirui Grass,
I've written them down on it.
Immortal was awesome that day.
He held you and stepped out of the punishment of thunder.
Luo Ge!
Luo Ge.
I just want to check on you.
I know that
our power is against each other, and
I shouldn't have come to you.
But I'm worried.
I just want to see you.
And Weirui Grass...
I planted it for you.
Wan Sui said you let me have it.
You suffered three thunderbolts
for me.
You need it more than I do.
Luo Ge,
I just want to see you.
Luo Ge, are you okay?
The truth is not clear yet.
You can't leave.
But if I don't leave,
you'll get hurt.
Do you think I'm you,
who gets hurt when you don't pay attention?
I didn't want to.
I didn't expect that fate would mess with us like this.
Lu Li is like this. You are the same.
Are you...
Are you okay?
The conflict of power between us
is not as serious as what Immortal Master has said.
I will investigate this matter.
You don't need to worry about it.
Okay.
I will stay
to investigate
who hurt Immortal Master.
I will prove to everyone that
I'm innocent.
I will prove that
you didn't trust the wrong person for your own good.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I was just thinking
how you will find the murderer.
This person wants to set me up.
In other words,
he failed to frame me
this time,
he will probably
kill me himself.
So,
let me be the bait.
Let's catch him in a trap.
What do you think?
It is a bad idea.
We've alerted the enemy.
How can you lure him?
You're right.
Maybe he has a personal grudge against Immortal Master.
How about investigating from here?
You don't need to worry about this.
I will investigate it.
Don't act rashly for the time being.
And this person must hate you.
What is this?
This is Wang Bell.
Remember to take it with you.
If you are in danger,
Moon Bell will be able to sense it.
And they will monitor your every move.
Does it mean that
Moon Bell will know whatever I say?
So,
don't talk about me behind my back.
I will speak and act cautiously.
I will speak less.
These days,
you just need to merge your air with it
and stay close to it.
Stay close to it?
At here?
Okay.
Your brother and future sister-in-law are fine.
Are you relieved now?
My brother must have been seriously injured
this time.
You imagine things
just because he didn't let you in.
At that time,
why didn't you play a little trick
and go inside?
I wanted to go inside.
But when I thought that
my brother lied to me
because he didn't want me to worry about him,
I could put up with everything.
Our little fairy
has grown up.
By the way,
remember to remind Liu Shao.
She must take good care of my brother.
If my brother is unhappy,
or he loses weight,
I will take my brother back.
Take him away.
Are you eating bitter gourds in the mortal world?
Are you silly because you have stayed in Immortal Palace for too long?
You can't even tell the difference between melons and bitter gourds.
But these look bitter.
I've planted all kinds of plants.
This is obviously a melon.
Try it if you don't believe me.
Thank you, Master.
The sisters
are both tricky.
Girl,
your things have all been packed.
In the next few days,
follow Immortal's words.
Where do I live?
Sleep on the floor.
Sleep on the floor?
Here is so big but you want me to sleep on the floor.
What is this?
Mandarin ducks?
Wan Sui is rubbernecking.
What mandarin ducks?
Well...
they are
ducks.
What are you doing?
At night,
the dew is heavy and there are many mosquitoes.
This
can calm your nerves and repel mosquitoes.
But
the wind is too strong.
I'm afraid it'll blow out the lamp.
This is Immortal Palace.
There's no trouble which is in the mortal world.
Even if
there is no mosquitoes,
it can light up a corner.
Then
it won't be so dark at night.
Night and day are natural.
Why should it be bright at night?
If you follow the laws of day and night,
why do you read and write at night?
Then why do we have the moon?
Isn't the moon natural?
Let me tell you.
When I was young,
my father used to do business.
Every day when he returned home,
it was after midnight.
My mother
put a light
at the door
to tell my father
no matter how late he came back,
someone would be waiting for him at home.
What do you mean by lighting a lamp?
With I lighting such a lamp,
you won't feel lonely.
Well...
As the saying goes,
the moon is bright or dim and she may wax or wane
But I hope
people can be reunited most of the time.
In this way,
you can be a deity earlier.
Liu Shao has returned to Xiyin Mountain.
It looks like you can do nothing with her.
We don't know
who will win now.
You have some guts.
I admire you.
You left Waterside Pavilion.
It looks like Fairy Luo Ning
still can't defeat you.
What is this?
It is for my master, Lu Sheng.
Today is his death anniversary.
No matter what,
he brought me and Lu Li up.
If it weren't because of him,
Lu Li wouldn't be the closest person to me.
Unfortunately,
Lu Li doesn't think you're his closest person.
And now, Lu Li
has become Luo Ge.
You're not in his heart.
It's okay.
I won't let him leave me,
even if I have to make him a walking dead.
As an immortal,
I am trapped by the spell in the mortal world
and can't be free.
Since you're familiar with her scent,
follow her from now on.
If one day
she and I are in danger at the same time,
You can only stay by her side.
Protecting her
is protecting me.
Luo Ge.
With Wang Bell on the side,
it feels like
you are always beside me.
I feel so relieved.
When you are in danger in the future,
you can use your power to activate Wang Bell.
Then, Moon Bell on me can sense it.
By the way,
you said that that person hates me
and she has the aura of my Sun Spirit.
Now it seems that
she got Sun Fragments from you.
Since she could know these
and got the fragments,
she must know you well.
Do you have anyone in mind?
Bai Feng.
But...
how could she be so capable?
She can't do it alone.
So we need to get the evidence.
The key is to lure out the person behind her.
This person
is also the one who Xie Lingqi refused to tell us
even if he was thrown into Bone Melting Pool.
I keep my promise and never turn you in.
But you...
but you watch me
suffer here. I can't die or survive.
Why?
Xie Lingqi,
you know how difficult it is
to deal with the immortal.
You need to give me some time.
You can actually hear me
and answer me.
Are you in Immortal Palace?
Not only am I in Immortal Palace,
but also in a place you can't imagine.
You are so capable.
Let me out!
I have a treasure.
I have Ao Hen's son.
For a thousand years,
Ao Hen fed him countless demon energy.
His demon power is quite great.
Ao Hen is so generous.
Fortunately, we found him first.
If her son wakes up,
I'm afraid he'll be a disaster for Immortal Palace.
Seal him.
Yes.
As long as you cultivate it,
you'll have another master to work for you.
Ao Yin?
That's right.
Matters need to be managed one by one.
After I finish what I am doing,
I will come to save you.
Don't go.
Let me out!
Someone is waiting for me.
A person is waiting for me.
She is waiting for me to save her.
It's been a thousand years.
Immortal,
I picked flowers according to your order.
Put it by Xuan Ling Wood.
I even picked the most powerful one.
Liu Shao has touched it.
I'm afraid there's still her scent on it,
so I asked you to bring some flowers
to remove her scent.
There should not be any other scent
in my place.
Yes.
Xuan Ling Wood is strong.
The flowers need to be wrapped with magic power.
Otherwise, it will burn the flowers.
Yes.
I'm incompetent.
I'll change it now.
No need.
Your cultivation is nothing more than this.
You may leave.
Yes.
You said Luo Ge asked you to get close to Xuan Ling Wood
and let you use your power.
He seldom talks so much to me,
so I was sure he was weird
and didn't use my power on purpose.
That's why I was burnt.
He's suspicious of you.
No way.
I did a good job.
You must have heard about Xuan Ling Wood absorbing demon energy
from Lu Sheng, right?
My master mentioned Immortal Palace,
so I was especially careful.
The power in your body
is mixed with Ao Hen's demon energy.
You burnt yourself deliberately
to prevent
Xuan Ling Wood from absorbing your spiritual power,
and Luo Ge from finding out that
you're related to the demonic realm,
right?
Then I wasn't wrong at all.
You were wrong,
totally wrong.
Let me ask you.
What does Xuan Ling Wood need to grow?
Immortals water it with spiritual power.
It doesn't need water.
Ridiculous.
No matter how the world change,
water is the origin of everything.
Even if he is Luo Ge,
he still needs to use his power to create rain
to nourish Xuan Ling Wood.
When you got close to Xuan Ling Wood,
there should be a lot of dew
on the leaves.
These
are made of Luo Ge's spiritual power.
As long as it's on you,
it can still take away your power
without you noticing it.
So,
he was testing me.
It was not testing.
He took such evidence from you
because he was certain that you were the suspect.